

#### Profile

Passionate about coding with 5 years experience in Web Design and Mobile Development. I'm always looking for the coolest and most recent programming technology to learn and use for my upcoming projects.

Currently i'm collaborating with an italian startup while i pursue new opportunities and can be reached either through linkedin (link on the right), by phone at +34 685399482 or on skype at @scratur3

#### Technologies i use:

#### Front end:

- HTML5, CSS3, SASS, Javascript, ES6/7, Web components.
- Frameworks: AngularJS, ReactJS, EmberJS, React Native.
- Libraries: Lodash, JWT, jQuery.
- Build Tools: NPM, YARN, Webpack, Browserify, Gulp.
- Templating: EJS, Handlebars.
- Hybrid app frameworks: Ionic, Cordova, OnsenUi

#### Back end:

- · Node.js, BackboneJS
- Frameworks: ExpressJS.

### Databases & query builders:

 MongoDB, GraphQL, MySQL, PostegreSQL, CouchDB, Knex. (bookshelf.js, sequelize, mongoose)

#### Infrastructure:

• Docker, Amazon Web Services (AWS), Lambda (Serverless framework)

#### CI/CD:

Gitlab CI/CD, Jenkins, Travis CI, CircleCI

#### Testing:

• Jasmine, Karma, Mocha.

# Employment History

### Senior Full Stack Javascript Developer at VISUP, (Remote)

November 2018 — Present

Products developed at VISUP:

- https://www.trueflu.co/home

#### Tech stack:

- FrontEnd:
  - Angular 7, TypeScript, Angular Universal(ssr)

#### **Details**

Calle Berlina 1, Costa De Antigua, 35610, Spain, +34 685399482 paolo.mangia.dev@gmail.com

Date / Place of birth

1993-09-07 Milano

Nationality

Italian

**Driving license** 

В

#### Links

Linkedin

StackOverflow

Github

Facebook

Instagram

Blog

**Team Website** 

#### Skills

Javascript

HTML5

CSS/SASS

AngularJS

ReactJS

Golang

Rust

NodeJS

MongoDB

GraphQL

SQL

#### Languages

English

Backend:	Italian
Serverless, Knex DB, Bookshelf.js	Spanish
Code Versioning - CI/CD:	French
• gitlab, gitlab CI/CD	
infrastructure:	
Amazon Web Services	
Management tools:	
Asana, Slite, Everhour	

### Full Stack Javascript Developer (Remote) at ASAP Italia, Roma

February 2018 — August 2018

Development of Condominiums managing application by the name of condexo.

tech stack:

- Front end:

HTML5, CSS3, SASS, Javascript, ES6, Web components.

Frameworks: AngularJS, ReactJS.

Build Tools: Webpack, Browserify, NPM, Gulp.

Templating: EJS,.

- Back end:

Node.js.

Frameworks: ExpressJS.

- Databases:

MongoDB.

- Testing:

Jasmine, Karma, Mocha.

- Source code management:

Git, Github, Gitlab.

more infos: http://www.condexo.it

### Full Stack Developer at PWC Italy, Milano

January 2017 — September 2017

Collaborated in the development of a Blockchain-based strong authentication application called StrongAuth.

StrongAuth is a mobile authorisation system that connects a traditional application of Public Key Infrastructure (PKI) with immutability and security of the Blockchain.

Technologies used:

- Front end:

HTML5, CSS3, SASS, Javascript, ES6, Web components.

Libraries: jQuery, Lodash. Frameworks: AngularJS.

Build Tools: Webpack, Browserify, NPM, Gulp.

Templating: EJS,.

Hybrid app frameworks: Ionic, Cordova

- Back end:

Node.js.

Frameworks: ExpressJS.

- Databases:

MongoDB.

- Testing:

Jasmine, Karma, Mocha.

- Source code management:

Git, Github, Gitlab.

### Full Stack Developer at TIP srls, Milan

June 2016 — July 2017

TIP is a Private Asset Sharing Platform that unleashes the power of Permissioned Blockchain TIP is a new mobile asset sharing platform that, leveraging blockchain technology, provides better performances (in terms of transactions-per-second) and reduces IT costs compared to current systems. It also guarantees a high security level due to an innovative technology solution implemented.

#### Technologies used:

- Front end:

HTML5, CSS3, SASS, Javascript, ES6, Web components.

Libraries: jQuery, Lodash. Frameworks: AngularJS.

Build Tools: Webpack, Browserify, NPM, Gulp.

Templating: EJS,.

Hybrid app frameworks: Ionic, Cordova

- Back end:

Node.js.

Frameworks: ExpressJS.

- Databases:

MongoDB.

- Testing:

Jasmine, Karma, Mocha.

- Source code management:

Git, Github, Gitlab.

### Full Stack Developer at SiComunicaWeb, Milano

May 2015 — April 2016

- Wordpress Development
- PSD to HTML
- CMS dev

## Education

## Informatics, ITIS Molinari, Milano

September 2010 — July 2015

While studying at ITIS Molinari i've developed strong programming and networking skills that gave me the base to expand further my knowledge with more indepth IT topics.

### **1** References

Sano Musab hijazi from Innovation Technologies Group Srl sano.hijazi@itechnologiesgroup.com

# https://paolomangiadev.eu

**Personal Blog** 

January 2018 — January 2018

# https://netglitch.com

**Team Website** 

January 2018 — January 2018